Kei'ichiro Yamamoto UX Design & Research

keiichiro.yamamoto@outlook.ca Toronto, ON, Canada 647.947.9324 keiyamamoto.ca

Objective

To enter the field of user experience design as a junior designer or researcher and work alongside a team that values and learns from the user's interactions with a system; and uses that knowledge to build a compelling story driven experience.

EDUCATION

Master of Information

University of Toronto

Graduation: June 2017

Relevant Coursework: user interface design, usability testing, user centered design, user-centered research methodologies, data analytics, information architecture, participatory design *Has also completed an Honors Bachelor of Arts at the University of Toronto

Certificate in Digital Media

Sheridan College

Graduation: May 2015

Relevant Coursework: **web design**, **design thinking**, audio production, **game design & theory**, film production & theory

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graphic Design and Marketing Specialist MitoCanada Foundation

June 2016 - October 2016

Supported the second-in command by creating marketing materials used for fundraiser campaigns, events, websites and social media. Helped raise \$20,000 in a fundraiser campaign. Skills used: HTML/CSS, Adobe Creative Suite, Writing

AV and IT Support

University of Toronto Psychiatry Department

October 2015 - April 2016

Managed the UofT Psychiatry Department's media server and created multimedia content for department's promotional use. Skills used: Adobe Creative Suite, HTML/CSS

Technical Director

CFRE Radio

May 2013 - August 2015

Managed and maintained the radio station's technical needs, web server and broadcast server. Provided recording and mastering for artists as well as consultation and directing for live stage technical setups. Directed a concert with over 300 attendees. Also ran a radio show about Japanese Indie music. Skills used: HTML/CSS, Problem Solving, Negotiation

PROJECTS

UX Designer

Office of Chief Health Innovation Strategist (OCHIS)

January 2016 - April 2016

Won over a difficult stakeholder by designing clickable wireframes to a browser-based health technology crowd funding platform and conducting participatory design sessions. Skills used: User Research, Negotiation, Presentations / Pitching

UX Designer

University of Toronto Career Center

January 2017 - April 2017

Convinced stakeholders to redesign UofT's "Career Navigator" site by presenting user research backed alignment diagrams and developing wireframes that helped students find the specific information they needed easier.

Skills used: User Research, Presentations / Pitching, Axure, Balsamia, User-Centered Methods, Adobe Creative Suite

Coordinator

Tokyo 7th Subs

February 2016 - Present

Leads a team of 7 individuals to create translated content for Japanese mobile game "Tokyo 7th Sisters" and develop an English translation patch. Has over 400 active users. Skills used: Project Management, User Research

SKILLS

Technical Skills

Axure, **Balsamiq**, HTML/CSS, **Adobe Photoshop**, **Adobe Illustrator**, **Adobe Premiere**, Adobe After Effects, inVision

Soft Skills

Writing, **Presentations / Pitching, Project Management, User Research**, Negotiation, Problem Solving, **User-Centered Methods**

About me

- Is a fluent Japanese speaker.
- Plays way too many indie games.
- Is really bad at singing but still will (and loves) to go karaoke.
- Values hard work, positive mental attitude and strong teamwork above all